<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Projects &#8211; Saurabh Freelancing Catalogue</title>
	<atom:link href="https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing</link>
	<description>Software Solution &#124;&#124; Web Devlopment</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:56:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Projects &#8211; Saurabh Freelancing Catalogue</title>
	<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Divisima</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/divisima/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5593</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Beauty - eCommerce - Fashion
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Divisima is a fantastic, modern, trendy and elegant free clothing website template. It suits fashion eCommerce stores best, but you can effortlessly use it to sell men fashion, accessories, bags, shoes and other items. Divisima is a simple to use template that you can alter to your branding needs in a small breeze. That said, make sure you enrich Divisima with your signature style and make it your own.</p>



<p>With an enticing and unique full-screen slider, you will win over new potential shoppers easily. Moreover, Divisima comes with a drop-drown menu, cart, checkout and contact pages, blog section and a widget-rich footer. Link your website with all your social media accounts and increase your potential through the roof. Start your online clothing store with Divisima and realize your idea once and for all.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ogani</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/ogani/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bootstrap Templates - Business, eCommerce - Food / Drinks]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Ogani is an outstanding, clean and modern organic food website template for building an impactful eCommerce page. Not only do you have the design predefined, but Ogani also comes with plenty of features and functions for saving yourself additional time and effort. For instance, along with selling goods, you can even start a compelling and educational blog that will further promote healthy living. You came to the right place if that is on your to-do list, as Ogani will be of tremendous help.</p>



<p>Moreover, Ogani ensures a mobile-ready and cross-browser compatible layout and is lightweight for exceptional performance. A few other amenities of this beautiful site canvas include a top bar, carousels, different internal eCommerce pages, and a contact section. Indeed, the latter contains Google Maps and contact form.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ashion</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/ashion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5560</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bootstrap Templates - eCommerce - Fashion]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Starting online with a clothing brand requires the fashion design website template, Ashion. Thanks to the predefined page layouts and features, this will save you a lot of time and energy. Also, with Ashion, you do not need to worry about current web regulations, like responsiveness and cross-browser compatibility. The tool sports all the latest regulations out of the box.</p>



<p>Moreover, Ashion rocks all sorts of great features that you can use and reuse. From countdown timer and slider to drop-down menu, social media icons, and Instagram-ready feed, it’s all available for your convenience. Ashion also does not miss a contact form and Google Maps. If you are ready to get the ball rolling like a pro, consider taking a clever shortcut with a fashion design website template, Ashion.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Essence</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/essence/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5554</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bootstrap Templates - eCommerce
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>End your search for the best clean eCommerce website template with our fantastic tool, Essence. With Essence, you have it all in the apple pie order for a shopping experience like none. The template is responsive, retina-ready, and powered by Bootstrap for the flexibility and stability you need. Creating a top-notch online shop with Essence is something you can do right away.</p>



<p>From a super fine home page to other inner sections for shop, product and checkout, Essence has it all at your disposal. There is also a subscription form in the footer and a full fashion blog included in the kit. Once you blend the supreme web design with your unbeatable items, success awaits you.<a href="https://colorlib.com/wp/template/essence/#"></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coza Store</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/coza-store/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 14:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5546</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Business - eCommerce]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coza Store online fashion store website template is your best approach to realizing it when it comes to selling apparel. It is a minimal eCommerce website template with elegance and simplicity being its main characteristics. But there is way more to Coza Store than just the two. Displaying items on the web has never been more attention-grabbing. The web design ensures buyers undergo a distraction-free shopping experience no matter the device.</p>



<p>Coza Store is responsive and stacked with various handy and powerful features. See its beauty in action by heading over to the preview page. If fashion is your passion, now you know how to turn it into a lucrative business. Start with Coza Store and see an unbelievable outcome.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Book Selling</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/book-selling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 13:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5540</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bootstrap 5 - eCommerce]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Book Selling is the best bookstore website template that you can employ for starting working on your business without doing it from scratch. The tool rocks many great features that will help you stand out. It is also a Bootstrap 5 template, so you know the layout is fully responsive, running smoothly on mobile screens.</p>



<p>Other goodies of BookSelling are slider, carousels, back to top button, floating navigation, newsletter section and social icons. There are also additional inner eCommerce pages, blog and contact section to work with. Feel free to style and beautify Book Selling to your liking and create an enviable bookstore website. The options are endless, so take BookSelling to your total advantage.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fashi</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/fashi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5534</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[eCommerce - Fashion]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>With a fashion eCommerce website template, Fashi, you can now start an online business quickly. At least when it comes to the design part of your online store, you do not have to worry about that anymore. Let Fashi take care of it in full with its trendy and sophisticated look. Thanks to the high adaptability of this nifty site canvas, you will not even want to change anything. However, Fashi is brandable, too.</p>



<p>Moreover, the list of features and functions is vast. Fashi has a slider, many practical inner page layouts, a countdown timer, social media icons, and a drop-down menu. You can also start a blog announcing new product drops, sharing outfits, and other whatnots. Last but not least, Fashi includes Google Maps and a functional contact form.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalshop</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/capitalshop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 13:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/?post_type=rainbow_projects#038;p=5414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bootstrap 5 · eCommerce · Fashion]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Capitalshop is an engaging fashion store website template for men, women, or general online shops. The template’s structure is user-friendly, so you can quickly get the most out of it. In addition to that, even if you would like to create a website for an apparel brand, that’s what you can bring to fruition, too. Capitalshop is here for everyone, whether a beginner or a professional coder and developer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pillow Mart</title>
		<link>https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/travel-app-design-creativity-application/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Saurabh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 20:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://github-saurabh0.github.io/Freelancing/projects/mobile-app-landing-design-service-copy-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[E-COMMERCE - Project]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-left">Pillow Mart, as the name suggests, is a pillows website template design for online stores. Along with selling pillows, you can also use Pillow Mart for other stuff, like beds, mattresses and similar. In addition to that, if you fancy the creative and minimal design of Pillow Mart, you can indeed fine-tune it further and utilize it for a different eCommerce website. The options are right at your fingertips</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
